Faster & Faster is a documentary film directed by Mark Neale.
Faster & Faster brilliantly captures the events which made the 2003 and 2004 MotoGP seasons so extraordinary: the tire-smoking arrival of the 215mph Ducati missiles; the shocking death of rising star Daijiro
Kato; the drama of Sete Gibernau's wild battles with Valentino Rossi; and the Italian's switch from the all-conquering Honda to the underdog Yamaha – a move which was to seal the Rossi legend.
This is the story of an epic time in MotoGP, in the words and
actions of the world's greatest motorcycle racers.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Ewan McGregor.
Self, played by John Hopkins.
Self, played by Valentino Rossi.
Self, played by Garry McCoy.
Self, played by Sete Gibernau.
Self, played by Max Biaggi.
Faster, Pussycat!
is a 1965 American exploitation film directed by Russ
Meyer and co-written by Meyer and Jack Moran.
It follows three go-go dancers who embark on a spree of
kidnapping and murder in the California desert.
The film is known for its violence, provocative gender roles, and
eminently quotable "dialogue to shame Raymond Chandler".
It is also remembered for the performance of star Tura Satana, whose character Richard Corliss called "the
most honest, maybe the one honest portrayal in the Meyer canon and certainly the scariest".
Faster, Pussycat!
was a commercial and critical failure upon its initial release, but it has since
become widely regarded as a cult classic and influential film.